{
    "id": "385de1b729434072b8e5f2f8ed4434aa",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Is anybody ............................. home?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I met him .............................. Tokyo.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They have a cottage ........................... the hills.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "There is a picture ........................... page six.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "There is a library ......................... the corner of the street.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Their office is ................................. the first floor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Many a man has drowned ........................... the sea.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "There were very few vegetarian dishes ............................ the menu.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "There was a cat sleeping ............................. the corner of the room.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I met her ............................. a conference.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "There were books lying ............................. the floor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is that boy .............................. the front row?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}